# ZEKEATSIKELIANOSDOTCOM

As a designer and a programmer, I strive to produce work that is functional and aesthetic. I enjoy working in stimulating environments with people who are passionate about what they do, and I want my work to inspire people creatively and intellectually. Over the last ten years I've worked in a variety of disciplines including print, environmental and interactive design. I'm a believer in open source and have authored numerous free libraries for various languages and frameworks.

## **TOOLBOX**

Ruby, Rails, Sinatra, jQuery, Actionscript, Processing, HAML/SASS, AWS (S3/EC2), Heroku, CouchDB, bash, svn, git, English, French, some Spanish, Flash, Illustrator, Photoshop, After Effects, OS X, Linux.

#### **EXPERIENCE**

#### Senior Developer, Gemini SBS: New York, NY — January 2009 - Present

Gemini SBS is a small employee-owned company that builds web-based software for non-profit organizations. I design, code, and manage Rails and Sinatra applications and webservices, many of which have a strong GIS component.

#### Developer, ELC Technologies: Santa Barbara, CA — January 2007 - March 2008

ELC is a consultancy providing Rails development services to Fortune 1000 companies. As a developer at ELC I oversaw the design, development, and maintenance of enterprise-level applications. I was exposed to many of the increasingly popular tenets of agile web development, including pair programming, scrum management and iterative development cycles.

#### Interactive Director, Ideum: Corrales, NM — April 2006 - November 2006

Ideum is a small new media outfit working for museums, educational institutions, nonprofit organizations and socially responsible companies. As Interactive Director, I oversaw the production of a variety of educational and humanitarian projects and worked extensively with Flickr and Google mashups.

## Designer/Developer, Rome & Gold Creative: Albuquerque, NM — August 2002 - May 2006

Rome & Gold Creative is a branding agency working in a wide array of media. I worked as Lead Web Designer/Developer and Junior Print Designer, focusing primarily on developing database-driven websites with user-friendly content management interfaces, but also doing print, clothing, environmental, and game design.

## English Teacher, French Government: L'Isle sur la Sorgue, France — September 2001 - May 2002

I taught English at a public high school in Provence, left to my own devices to encourage teenage students to converse openly about American culture.

## Guru Factotum, Neogenesis Media: Albuquerque, NM — December 2000 - September 2001

Neogenesis was a documentary film production house. I worked primarily on post-video editing using discreet Combustion and After Effects, but also produced interactive CD-ROMs and Flash websites, and developed and maintained a networked rendering farm.

## **ACCOLADES**

My work has been published in numerous design books, Print Magazine's Regional Design Annual, How Magazine, and has been selected as a Yahoo! Pick of the Day. I won Wordnik.com's 2010 developer challenge in the education category for logophilia.org

#### **EDUCATION**

University of New Mexico: Fall 1999 - Spring 2001 Santa Barbara City College: Fall 2008 - Spring 2009

Machine Project: 2010

## REFERENCES

Wolf Klinker, former employer - wolfklinker@gmail.com; 805.886.6835 Robert Goldie, former employer - bobbygoldie@gmail.com; 505.720.4653 Joe Fazio, former employer - joe@givezooks.com; 805.705.2590